This surgery robot is carefully cutting
up and then stitching back together corn
and it could one day save your life.
This tiny little surgery is controlled
by human doctors watching through a
magnified camera. The robot helps take
the doctor's real movements, but then
scale them way down to smaller, more
precise ones. Smaller cuts means fewer
complications and [music] faster
recovery. Previous versions of this
robot could make cuts about the width of
your fingertip or a grape, but this one
is meant for surgeries 10 times smaller
than that. Meaning it could be used to
operate on tiny blood vessels and nerves
helping [music] reattach limbs or fix
nerve damage. So, if you want more
optimistic science and tech stories,
subscribe.